there are three beasts in the Book of
Revelation the first Beast Rises out of
the sea and dominates for 42 months at
the end of this 42-month period two
other beasts rise up one from the earth
and one from the abyss we understand
that beasts in the Bible represent
kingdoms so we're looking then for Three
Kingdoms three powers the first is to
dominate for 42 months and then the last
two come into prominence at the very
same time at the end of that 42-month
period so then in order to rightly
identify these two latter beasts we must
actually first identify the first beast
and to do that we're going to go back to
the Book of Revelation who is this first
Beast thank you Jesus for the cross I
want to welcome welcome each one of you
today those of you that are watching
from around the world we got a very
special message today as you can see on
the screen behind me today's message is
entitled America in Prophecy put a one
in the chat if you are ready to get into
the word of God today is going to be
this is going to be a Bible study all
right so however you take notes you want
to take notes make sure you got your pen
your iPad whatever it is we are going to
be getting pretty deep into the Bible
today because we're looking at a very
important subject that we need to
understand and if you have never heard
anything like this before I'm going to
encourage you to pay close attention if
you have heard this particular teaching
before still pay attention all right
there's a lot to learn a lot to cover
particularly dealing with the times we
are living in right now so with that
said let's go ahead and pray and then
we're going to open the word let's go
ahead and pray father bless us Lord as
we open your word today Lord please
speak through me again Lord I ask that
your word will be clear and Lord that
your words will be heard and you will be
seen we pray this in Jesus name amen
amen okay we're going to go
systematically through the scriptures
because I'm going to show you some very
important things regarding this question
this subject America in Prophecy we're
going to start by introducing you to
several beasts in the Book of Revelation
so let's go to the screen and we are
first going to talk about the beast from
the earth now if you're saying the beast
from the earth what is this don't worry
we're going to explain I'm going to
explain what a beast is in a moment but
I just want you to notice what
Revelation chapter 13 beginning with
verse 11 so here it says and I beheld
another Beast coming up out of the earth
and he had two horns like a lamb and he
spake as a dragon dragon and he
exerciseth all the power of the first
Beast before him so I just want you to
pause here and see that there is a beast
that comes before this beast from the
earth just keep that in mind so he
exercised all the power of the first
Beast before him and caused the Earth
and them that dwell therein to worship
the first Beast whose deadly wound was
healed and he doeth great Wonders that
he maketh Fire come down from heaven on
the earth in the sight of men and
deceive them that dwell in the Earth by
the means of those Miracles which he had
power to do in the side of the Beast
saying to them that dwell on the earth
that they should make an image to the
Beast which had the wound by a sword and
did live verse 15 and he had power to
give life unto the image of the Beast
that the image of the Beast should both
speak and cause that as many as would
not worship the image of the Beast
should be killed and he causeth all both
small and great rich and poor free and
bond to receive a mark in their right
hand or in their foreheads and that no
man might buy or sell save he that had
the Mark or the name of the Beast or the
number of his name finally verse 17 or
Verse 18 here is wisdom let him that has
understanding count the number of the
Beast for it is the number of a man and
his number is 6003 score and six meaning
600 so let's come back and I just want
you to to lock in your mind that this
first Beast is described as coming out
of the Earth but there is a beast that
comes before him we're not going to talk
about that Beast yet and we still have
identified what is a beast in the Book
of Revelation so just keep this in mind
this is the first Beast we're looking at
in terms of our study it is not the
first Beast presented in the Book of
Revelation but it's the first beast in
our study all right let's go to another
Beast we're going to go back to the
screen and now we're going to talk about
the beast from the abyss or the
bottomless pit this is a separate Beast
the Bible says here in Revelation 11:7
and when they shall have finished their
testimony now we don't know who that
they are we're going to get to that I
just want this is just introductory all
right and when they shall have finished
their testimony the Beast that ascendeth
out of the bottomless pit shall make war
against them and shall overcome them and
kill them and their dead bodies shall
lie in the street of that great city
which spiritually is called Sodom in
Egypt where also our Lord was crucified
reading on and they of the people and
kindreds and tongues and Nations shall
see their dead bodies three days and a
half and shall not suffer their dead
bodies to be put in Graves and they that
dwell upon the Earth shall rejoice over
them and make Merry and shall send gifts
unto one one another because these two
prophets tormented them that dwell on
the earth and after three days and a
half the spirit of life from God entered
into them and they stood upon their feet
and great fear fell upon them which saw
them and they heard a great voice from
Heaven saying unto them come up hither
and they ascended to heaven in a cloud
and their enemies beheld them and that
same hour there was a great earthquake
and the 10th part I want you to lock
this in here the 10th part of the city
fell and in the earthquake there was
slain of men 7,000 and the remnant were
AF frighted and gave glory to the god of
Heaven okay so let's come back for a
moment and uh what we just did in our
opening for this message is we look at
this Beast that is described as coming
up out of the earth and then we looked
at another Beast that is described as
coming up out of an abyss and there are
several things that both of these beasts
do we're going to get into that but I
want you to note one is from the and one
is from the abyss now our next question
is this let's go back to the screen the
question is this what is a beast
according to Bible prophecy what is a
beast according to Bible prophecy let's
go ahead and look at Daniel chapter 7
let me see if I can get rid of this here
for a moment okay Daniel 7:23 the Bible
says here thus he said the fourth Beast
shall be the fourth Kingdom upon the
Earth and shall shall devour from shall
be diverse from all kingdoms and shall
Devour the whole earth and tread it down
and break it in pieces now notice this
the very next verse Daniel 7:24 and the
T horns of this kingdom are 10 kings
that shall arise and another shall arise
after them and he shall be diversed from
the first and shall subdue three kings
okay so here's what I'm doing here I'm
giving you I'm reading verses in their
entirety but I simply want you right now
to focus focus on the fact that a beast
in Bible prophecy represents a kingdom
or a nation okay a beast symbolizes a
kingdom or a nation and thus we find in
the Book of Revelation chapter 13 that
there is a beast or a nation described
as coming out of the earth and then
another Beast or Nation described as
coming up out of an abyss all right
let's come back to the screen for a
moment and I want you to understand that
Revelation chapter 13 is telling us
about the story of two Nations put a one
in the chat if you're following this so
far this is the story of two Nations so
now we ask a question our next question
is this what time period is pointed out
for these nations what time period is
pointed out for these nations now in
order to do this we're we're going to
have to go back to Revelation chapter 13
and now learn about the first beast in
Revelation chap 13 beginning with verse
one John says and I stood upon the sand
of the sea and saw a beast rise up out
of the sea having seven heads and 10
horns and upon his horns 10 crowns and
upon his heads the name of blasphemy so
now we're seeing there's another Beast
this one comes up out of the sea now if
were paying attention when we read about
that beast from the earth that was
around Revelation
13:1 this beast from the sea is in
Revelation 13 verse1 so when the Bible
says that this second beast from the
earth exercise the power of the first
Beast before it it's talking about the
beast from the sea whatever Kingdom this
might be this Kingdom in Revelation 13:1
is described as rising in out of the sea
having seven heads 10 horns and let's
continue to read let's continue to read
verse two and the Beast which I saw was
like unto a leopard and his feet were as
the feet of a bear and his mouth the
mouth of a lion and the dragon gave him
his power and his seat and great
Authority verse three and I saw one of
his heads as it were wounded to death
and his deadly wound was healed and all
the world wondered after the Beast and
they worshiped the dragon which gave
power unto the Beast saying who is like
unto the Beast who is able to make war
with him and there was given to him a
mouth speaking great things and
blasphemies and power was given unto him
to continue 40 and2 months 40 and two
months keep that number in mind verse
six and he opened his mouth in blasphemy
against God to blaspheme his name and
his Tabernacle and them that dwell in
heaven and it was given unto him to make
war with the Saints and to overcome them
and power was given him over all
kindreds and tongues and Nations verse
eight and all that dwell upon the Earth
shall worship Him whose names are not
written in the Book of Life of the lamb
slain from the foundation of the world
so I want you to come back to the screen
now and we're about to make we're about
to establish our first crucial point
which is this the second beast of Bible
prophecy the second beast in Revelation
13 the Beast that rises out of the earth
Rises after the Beast that rolls out of
the sea we're told that the Beast that
rose out of the sea dominated for this
period of 40 months meaning this second
beast is going to rise into Power
sometime after or towards the end of the
42 months if this makes sense put a one
in the chat for me please we're simply
trying to identify the time period of
this second beast the beast from the
Earth all right put a one in the chat if
you're following so far the beast from
the sea is said to dominate for 42
months it is at the end of this of this
42 months that Revelation 1311 int
introduces us to this second beast
rising up out of the earth okay so far
so good let's go ahead and I want you to
notice with me the beast from the abyss
also has a time period let's notice in
Revelation 13:11 and there was given me
a reed like unto a rod and the angel
stood saying rise and measure the temple
of God and the Altar and them that
worship therein but the court which is
without the temple leave out and measure
it not for it is given unto the Gentiles
and the holy city shall they tread Under
Foot
402 40 and two months this is the same
time period come back with me for a
moment is the same time period described
regarding this first Beast which was to
dominate 40 and2 prophetic months all
right so the Bible here in Revelation 13
is describing this trampling of the
people of God for 42 months come back
with me to the screen notice verse three
and I will give power unto my two
witnesses and they shall prophesy a
thousand
23 score days clothed in sackcloth that
number actually equals out to 160 days
if you divide that by 30 you get two
months this is the same time period that
was allotted to that first Beast that
came up out of the sea so now Watch What
Happens Next come back with me to the
screen verse four these are the two
olive trees talking about these two
witnesses whoever they are we're going
to get into that these are the two olive
trees and the two candlesticks standing
before the god of the earth and if any
man will hurt them fire proceedeth out
of out of their mouth and devour their
enemies and if any man will hurt them he
must in this manner be killed these have
power to shut Heaven that it rain not in
the days of their prophecy and they have
power over Waters to turn them to blood
and to Smite the Earth with all plagues
as often as they will now watch this and
when they shall have finished their
testimony when do these two witnesses
finish their testimony put it in chat
for me please how long were they to
testify clothed and sacko let me go back
let me go back I will give power unto my
two witnesses and they shall prophesy
how long 1,23 score days 42 months and
it is at the end of this 42 Monon period
that the Bible says the Beast that
ascendeth out of the bottomless pit
shall make war against them and shall
overcome them and kill them so here is
the point that I need you to understand
here the beast from the abyss I want to
put this up on the screen the beast from
the abyss as well as the beast from the
earth both rise after the beast from the
sea which was said to dominate 42 months
meaning let's come back to come back
here come back to me listen both the
beast from the abyss and the Beast from
the Earth we can expect them to be
rising at the same time at the end of
the rain of that beast from the sea
which is said to rule for 42 months if
you're following put a one in the chat
I'm gonna I'm going to simplify this for
you okay there are three beasts in the
Book of Revelation the first Beast Rises
out of the sea and dominates for 42
months at the end of this 42-month
period two other beasts rise up one from
the earth and one from the abyss we
understand that beasts in the Bible
represent kingdoms so we're looking then
for Three Kingdoms three powers the
first is set to dominate for 42 months
and then the last two come into
prominence at the very same time at the
end of that 42-month period so then in
in order to rightly identify these two
latter beasts we must actually first
identify the first beast and to do that
we're going to go back to the Book of
Revelation who is this first Beast
notice with me again how John describes
his beast and I stood upon the sand of
the sea and saw a beast rise up out of
the sea having seven heads and 10 horns
and upon his horns 10 crowns and upon
his heads the name of blasphemy and the
Beast which I saw was like unto a
leopard his feet were as the feet of a
bear his mouth as the mouth of a a lion
and the dragon gave him his power and
his seat and great Authority and I saw
one of his heads as it were wounded to
death and his deadly wound was healed
and all the world wandered after the
Beast now John is actually borrowing
from a vision that came from The Book of
Daniel and if we go back to the Book of
Daniel chapter 7 beginning with verse
one the Bible says in the first year of
Bel Cesar king of Babylon Daniel had a
dream and visions of his head upon his
bed then he wrote the dream and told the
sum of the matters Daniel spake and said
I saw in my vision by night and behold
the Four Winds of the heavens strove
upon the great sea so notice this vision
is occurring where at the great sea
where did John see this beast in
Revelation 13:1 rising up out of the sea
very good we're going to see beloved
this is the very same Beast come back
with me to verse three and four great
beasts came up from the sea diverse one
from another the first was like a lion
and had Eagle's Wings and I beheld till
the wings thereof were plucked and it
was lifted up from the earth and made to
stand upon the feet as a man and a man's
heart was given to it so remember that
beast in Revelation 13 looked like a
lion it rose up out the sea and it
looked like a lion watch what Daniel
says about the second beast and behold
another Beast a second like to a bear
remember that beast in Revelation 13 did
not only look like a lion it also looked
like a bear and it raised itself up on
one side and had three ribs in the mouth
of it between the teeth of it and they
said thus unto it arise and devour much
flesh after this I beheld un low another
like a leopard remember that beast in
Revelation 13 also looked like a leopard
this Beast according to Daniel 7 had
upon the back of it four wings of a foul
the Beast also had four heads and
Dominion was given to it and then Daniel
sees one last Beast after this I saw in
the night visions and behold a fourth
Beast Dreadful and terrible and strong
exceedingly and it had great iron teeth
and it devoured and break in pieces and
stamp the residue with the feet of it
and it was diverse from all the beasts
that were before it and it had how many
horns everybody 10 horns 10 horns come
back with me come back with me for a
moment in the Book of Daniel these four
beasts represent four Kingdoms in the
time of Daniel those kingdoms are the
following the lion was a symbol of the
Babylonian Empire in the days that
Daniel was writing put that in the chat
for me please the lion equal Babylon the
bear would have been the nation that
came after Babylon and that would have
been the MEO Persian Empire The Leopard
with foreheads would have represented
the king that overthrew the m and
Persians which would have been the
Grecian EMP Empire so lion Babylon bear
Meo Persia leopard Greece and the fourth
Beast with the 10 horns would symbolize
the kingdom that took over after Greece
that would be the kingdom of Rome so
those four beasts would symbolize
Babylon met Persia Greece Rome now when
Rome fell it broke down into various
Barbarian tribes this this is what is
symbolized by the 10 horns among those
tribes were Nations that are existing
today one of them just please keep this
in mind one of them was called the
kingdom of the Franks which we would
know today as France please keep this in
mind France or the Franks was one of the
10 symbolically speaking those kingdoms
that came out of the fall of the Roman
Empire now let's go back to the screen
and I want should have notice this
Daniel 7:8 I considered the horns and be
behold there came up among them another
little horn before whom three of the
first horns were plucked up by the roots
and behold in this horn were eyes like
the eyes of a man and a mouth speaking
great things so now we got to Simply ask
a question what kingdom let me go back
here for a moment what kingdom came out
of divided Rome that would rise up and
uproot three of 10 horns of those
kingdoms that were vying for power I
want you to note what the Bible says
continues to say about this little horn
notice verse 25 he shall speak great
words against the most high and shall
wear out or persecute the Saints of the
most high and think to change times and
laws and they shall be given into his
hand until a time times and the dividing
of time this is literally translated as
three and a half years or 1,000 days or
two months that means that whatever
whoever this little horn is John in the
Book of Revelation is seeing this as one
power and all we got to do is ask
ourselves what power of a spiritual
nature because if you're blaspheming
against the god of Heaven if you're
changing his laws and if you're
persecuting Saints and you're standing
in the place of God this must represent
a spiritual Kingdom the question is what
spiritual or religious Kingdom rose out
of Rome after the fall of the Roman
Empire within the breakdown of those 10
kingdoms it is none other than the
papacy the Roman Catholic Church which
by the way uprooted three of these
Powers they were the her the vandals and
the ostrogoths so let me break this down
for you as carefully as I can the Bible
says this little horn would uproot three
of the 10 it would also think to change
times and laws and if you do any study
at all in history you will know that the
papacy claims to have changed the
Sabbath from the seventh day of the week
to the first day of the week but that's
not even our Focus right now I want you
to note this the papacy had religious
conflicts with several of these
Barbarian tribes that came out of the
Roman Empire three of them were the
hereli the vandals and the ostrog gods
their conflict was over the nature of
Christ and the godhead and so what
happened was the P tried to eliminate
these because they too were catholic but
they were Aryan in nature and I'm not
going to get into what Aryan means right
now but simply to say this when they
uprooted that third power which would
have been the kingdom of the ostros the
year was 538 now if you're familiar with
history you might say the ostros they
reigned after 538 they didn't really
fall till around 550 something but I
need you to catch I need you to check
this out let's go back to the screen uh
the ostrogothic papacy was a period now
not what I just said the ostrogothic
papacy you say what is the ostrogothic
papacy it is a it was the papacy that
was put into place after the defeat or I
should say just before the defeat of the
ostrogothic Kingdom the ostrogothic
papacy was a period from 493 to what
Year everyone 7 where the papacy was
strongly influenced by the
ostrogothic kingdom if the pope was not
outright appointed by The ostrogothic
King The Selection and administration of
popes during this period was strongly
influenced by theodoric the great and
his successor AIC and theoh Hadad this
period terminated with Justinian ones
reconquest of Rome during the gothic war
and inaugurated the bantine papacy in
537 now come back with me I know this is
a lot of history to takeen but it is
crucial history the ostrogothic papacy
was still opposed to the Roman Catholic
Church at large because of their view of
the nature of Christ so when Justinian
conquered or drove out the ostros out of
Rome in Justinian puts in his own Pope
which is favorable to the Catholics and
what he does in essence is he introduces
the papacy the ostrogothic papacy comes
to an end now listen I'm bringing you to
a certain year and I need you to
understand this all right Pope syus
let's go back to the screen Pope
silverius who was the pope the last pope
of the ostrogothic kingdom was Bishop of
Rome from June 8 536 to his deposition
in 537 a few months before his death now
he died on December 2nd 5 the end of 537
why is it significant because even
though Pope vigilus come back to the
screen with me even though pop vigilus
which was the pope that was instituted
by Justinian himself even though he was
instituted in 537 according to Catholic
tradition you can't have two two living
popes at the so there was controversy
even over vilus says so it was not until
Pope Silvius died at the end of December
537 that vigil was officially seen as
the pope 38 now why have I worked so
hard to bring you to this year 538
because in Bible prophecy a day equals a
year in the Book of Daniel and the Book
of Revelation straight through a day is
always symbolic of a year meaning
1,260 days is actually
1,260 years and guess what happens if
you take 538 and add
1,260 years so 538 after that third horn
is officially uprooted and a new type of
papacy is put into place you count 1,260
years you come to the year
1798 let's go to the screen 538 to 1798
equals
1,260 years and what happened in the
year 1798 Napoleon's General birth of
year and 15,000 soldiers moved into the
Papal States unopposed and on February
10th
1798 encamped around the camp the walls
of Jerusalem three days later I'm sorry
the walls of Rome 3 Days Later berier
entered the city and took the Pope Pius
I 6 prisoner berthier demanded that the
pope abandon his temporal authority over
Rome and the Papal States and leave Rome
itself for good in other words the Papal
States that had dominated listen to me
y' and persecuted for over 1,200 years
1260 to be exact was abolished 1798 the
Bible says it this way a deadly wound
was received by this first Beast so this
now tells us that these two other beasts
that arise at the end of this Kingdom
should be arising into prominence
sometime around when can y'all help me
when should we be looking for the rise
of these other nations coming on the
scene prophetically speaking when should
we be looking for the significance of
these nations sometime around the end of
the 12 60 years meaning sometime in the
late 17 are y'all with me so far let's
go back let's go back to this beast from
the abyss remember what the Bible said
here I will give power unto my two
witnesses and they shall prophesy
1,23 score days clothed in sackcloth so
come back to the screen here's what we
know whoever these two witnesses are
they were prophesying at the same time
that the papal church was dominating
that's not 1 days literal days it's
1,260 what what everyone years and if
it's 1,260 years then there's one thing
we know about these two witnesses they
cannot be literal people because people
don't live
260 years put a one in the chat if you
caught that whatever these two witnesses
are it must represent something that is
symbolic L let's go back to the screen
please note with me again these are the
two olive trees and the two candlesticks
standing before the god of the earth and
if any man will hurt them fire
proceedeth out of their mouth and devour
them and devour their enemies do you
know Fire coming out of any people's
mouth no and if any man will hurt him he
must in he this manner be killed these
have power to shut Heaven that it rain
not in the days of their prophecy and
have power over Waters to turn them to
blood and to smite the Earth with all
plagues as often as they will and when
they shall have finished their testimony
the Beast that ascendeth out of the
bottomless pit shall make war against
them and shall overcome them and kill
them so let's break down the
significance of this Beast coming out of
an abyss first of all notice with me on
the screen this word Abyss or the
bottomless pit is the same word used to
describe the Earth before God began
creating on it in the beginning God God
created the Heaven and the Earth and the
Earth was without form and void and
darkness was upon the face of the deep
that word there for deep abusos is the
same word that is used to describe this
Abyss that the pit right that the Beast
rises from so we can think of it like
this then whatever Nation this is that
is being highlighted at this time at the
end of the 1260 is going to have
something to do listen to me with or
with the creation account please follow
me here follow me let's check out the
significance of these two witnesses the
Bible says Thy word is a lamp like a
Candlestick Thy word is a lamp unto my
feet and a light onto my path I'm going
to suggest to you that these two
witnesses are the word of God it was the
word of God that was testifying despite
what the papacy was doing during the
Dark Ages the word of God these were the
witnesses the old and the New Testament
these were the witnesses that were doing
their work their appointed work despite
what the papacy was doing during the
Dark Ages by the way the papacy did not
allow people to have copies of the Old
and New Testament you say Pastor are you
sure it's the word come back with me to
the screen notice again the Bible says
we have also a more sure word of
Prophecy where unto you do well that you
take heed as unto a light that shineth
in a dark place until the day Dawn and
the day star arises in your heart again
it's being compared to a Candlestick the
entrance of thy words giveth light it
giveth understanding to the simple what
about this Jesus said search the
scriptures for in them you think you
have eternal life and these are they
which testify of me what do Witnesses do
Witnesses testify Jesus himself said the
scriptures are his Witnesses they
testify of him the word of God testifies
of Christ so now watch this how does
this fit in with Revelation 11
Revelation 11:6 these have power to shut
Heaven that it Reign not in the days of
their prophecy you want to know who who
shut Heaven that it rained not in the
days of their prophecy It Was Elijah
James 3:17 Elijah was a man subject to
like passions as we are and he prayed
earnestly that it might not rain and it
rained not on the Earth by the space of
three years and 6 months and he prayed
again and the heaven gave rain and the
Earth brought forth her fruit all right
so hold on that is pointing us to Elijah
the fact that these Witnesses have power
to stop the rain what about turning
water to Blood come with me again
remember verse six which said they also
have power over Waters to turn them to
blood and to Smite the Earth with all
plagues that oftenness they will and
you'll know who did this in the Old
Testament it was Moses and the Lord
spake unto Moses saying unto Aaron take
thy rod and stretch out thine hand upon
the waters of Egypt and upon the streams
and upon the rivers and upon their ponds
and upon all their pools of water that
they may become blood and that there may
be blood throughout all the land of
Egypt both in the vessels of wood and in
the vessels of stone and so beloved I I
need you to catch this come with me
Moses was symbolic of the Elijah is
symbolic of the prophets what was the
Bible literally it is called the law and
the prophets these are the two witnesses
it's not literally Moses it's not
literally Elijah it's the word of God
also known as the law and the prophets
in fact in Romans chapter 3: 211 notice
what the scripture says here but now the
righteousness of God without the law is
manifested being witnessed by the law
and the prophets the law Moses and the
prophets Elijah so then when the Bible
is using these two witnesses speaking
about these two witnesses it's talking
about the word of God despite the lies
and the Darkness that was being promoted
by the church during the Dark Ages the
word of God was still doing its work now
how does this help us whatever power
this is that comes upon the scene at the
end of the
1,260 years must be a power that is
going to attack are y'all with me attack
the two witnesses so now all we got to
do is ask a simple question what nation
towards the end of the 1700s launched an
allout assault against the Bible against
Christianity against God against
everything that had to do with God
against the creation account and the
answer is let's just go to the screen on
October 5 1793 Christian Europe Europe
was rocked by the Revolutionary
government of France declaring the deest
blish or de christianization of France a
move specifically intended to remove the
influence of the Catholic Church Upon
France and the French people atheism
listen to me you guys atheism got its
launch atheism existed before the French
Revolution but it is in the French
Revolution that atheism became this
organized movement that was no longer
afraid to be in the to be out of the
closet and the French Revolution was in
essence a rejection of what the Catholic
church had been doing throughout the
1,260 years as well as a rejection of
the Bible altogether it is here that
Concepts about the creation account you
know what no the Bible isn't real and
God didn't create the world in six days
and and ath M got this push this it made
its major step onto the stage if you
will the French Revolution now y'all
ready to have your minds blown check
this out it was during the French
Revolution it was during the French
Revolution that to by the way the French
Revolution was a revolution about
freedom from religion put that word in
the chat for me please from freedom from
religion that's why this Beast is
described as rising out of the Abyss
it's going back to the creation account
and saying no God is not real the Bible
isn't real the word of God is not real
God is doesn't exists atheism that's the
thing the goddess of reason this was the
basis of the French Revolution it was a
revolution from religion so watch this
the papacy dominates 1,260 years and at
the end of that 1,260 years we now know
that at least one of these beasts the
beast from the abyss symbolizing the
French Revolution was a rebellion
against Christianity altogether it was
freedom from religion the terms left and
right the political term left and right
came out of the French Revolution you
want to know who they said represented
the left those who were in favor of the
Revolution those who were against
Christianity those who were against God
those who were against the papacy those
who were against anything religious they
were represented by they were called
literally look this up the political
terms that we use today left and right
came because those who were in favor of
the Revolution sat to the left of the
king and those who were in favor of the
king and in favor of the church sat to
the right this is the origin of the
terms left and right left representing
liberalism left representing a being
against God that's where it originates
now let's get to that beast from the
Earth let's get to that beast from the
earth notice with me Revelation 13: 11
and I beheld another Beast coming up out
of the earth and he had two horns like a
lamb and he spake as a dragon so far we
have very interesting resue I don't even
know if I said your name right but
France gave the Statute of Liberty to
the US very interesting very interesting
so far we have the beast from the sea
symbolizing the papacy at the end of the
rise of the papacy at the end of the the
reain of the papacy which ible says
would have a deadly wound but that
deadly wound would be healed we see the
rise of this beast from the abyss which
represents the French Revolution a
revolution against the Bible a
revolution against Christianity a
revolution against God towards the end
of the 1700s but now we got another
Beast rising up from the earth this one
looks like a lamb so now we got to
Simply ask ourselves what nation would
have been rising around the same time
but instead of rising out of the Abyss
anti-christian anti- God anti-bible this
nation looks like a lamb come on y'all
can I just end it here watch this who is
the Lamb symbolic of in a scripture
notice with me again John 1:29 the next
day John seeth Jesus coming unto him and
saith Behold the Lamb of God which
taketh away the sin of the world so the
lamb in the Bible is symbolic of Christ
so now all we need to do is ask
ourselves is there a nation that would
have come on the scene that was Rising
into Power towards the end of the 1700s
that claimed to represent Christianity
oh yes the United States of America the
United States of America while the
French Revolution is happening on one
hand the American Revolution is
happening on the other around the same
time period our first president 1789
interesting interesting watch this y'all
the B the bble says that even though he
had horns like a lamb he would speak as
a what come on this power would speak as
a dragon the American experiment we
might say was not based on freedom from
religion but it was based on freedom
what of religion put that word in the
chat for me of of so here you got two
different powers representing two
different systems one a ISM the left and
the other Christianity those in favor of
God and religion and now you can take a
look at what's happening in our nation
and what is a war against a war watch
this of the beast from the earth versus
the beast from the abyss to put it in
prophetic terms the very political war
struggle going on right now the Bible
prophesied it there are the principles
of the Abyss God doesn't exist God is
not real we want to do whatever we want
to do versus the principles of the beast
from the earth God is real but while
they're saying God is real they're
actually speaking like a dragon and how
can we see this because beloved from its
very Inception of this nation which
claim to be a Christian Nation how can
you claim to be a Christian Nation and
yet not afford Liberty how could you
claim to be a Christian Nation and yet
sell The Souls of men
how could you claim to be a God-fearing
nation and yet beat men and women to
death rap them and do so in the name of
Jesus with a Bible in your hand slaves
obey your masters using the Bible so we
see that from its very Inception while
it claimed the lambl likee principles it
was actually speaking like a dragon now
beloved we're not talking about people
we're talking about systems are you
understanding me what I'm saying beloved
is not that people in America are
everyone in America in our founding the
founding of America was corrupt there
was good in America and there was bad in
America but as a nation as a system the
Bible is speaking specifically about
protestantism that failed to rightly
represent Christ so now watch it listen
to me y'all the first Beast the Roman
Catholic system that's the Beast that
dominated during the Dark Ages the two
other beasts represents atheism and F
counterfeit Christianity in the name of
Jesus are y'all with me so far so now we
see that the Book of Daniel and the Book
of Revelation has brought us right up to
our very day where we're watching this
conflict between these two superpowers
if you will now follow me here cause
because here's where we're about to get
into the message notice with me this he
exercised all the power of the first
Beast before him and cause the Earth and
them that dwell therein to worship the
first Beast who deadly wound was healed
so the Bible is telling us that
Protestant America is going to end up
exising or
reestablishing what happened in the Dark
Ages meaning in the Dark Ages the papacy
was a church State system church and
state were United with the church
dominating the state and when that
happens what you have is persecution
that's why they persecuted the Saints of
the most high for a Time
times and a half the Bible is telling us
that in Protestant so-call Protestant
America this same thing is going to be
repeated people are going to say in
order to fight against the atheism and
the liberalism in our country we've got
to turn this nation back to God we've
got to enforce Christianity we've got to
put people who are Christians in power
and therefore we can set up a Christian
Society but beloved listen to me when
the church rules the state persecution
is sure to follow and this is exactly
what the Bible says is going to happen
are y'all following this listen notice
verse 15 Revelation 13:3 rather and he
doeth great wonders so that he maketh
Fire come down from heaven on the earth
in the sight of men and deceiveth them
that dwell on the Earth by the means of
those Miracles which he had power to do
in the sight of the Beast now I need
y'all to understand this right I need
you to understand that there is no way
that what I just said is going to happen
in America unless a miracle occurs you
don't understand you see how the left
and the right fight against each other
now there is no way there is no way that
this power described as a protestantism
that I'm not saying everyone's an
apostate Protestant I'm saying systems
that claim the Bible and yet do not
reflect
the character of God the Bible says that
this power is going to make all of
America do this and the whole world but
I need to let you know that is
impossible unless a miracle happens and
this is exactly what the Bible is saying
he doeth great wonders so they make fire
come down from heaven in the sight of
men and this is what convinces them now
I got to ask you a question how many of
you remember anywhere else in the Bible
that fire came down in the sight of men
you remember what prophet did that yes
Elijah come on let's go to the screen
then said Elijah unto the people I even
I only remain a prophet of the Lord but
baal's prophets are 50 men so these are
the 450 false prophets let them
therefore Elijah said give us two
Bullocks and let them choose one bullet
for themselves and cut it in pieces and
lay it on wood and put no fire under and
I will dress the other bulock and lay it
on wood and put no fire under going on
here's what he says you call on the name
of your gods and I will call on the name
of the Lord and the god that answers by
fa fire let him be God and all the
people answered and said it is well
spoken now they begin to do their thing
right Elijah said to the prophets of
baale choose your bulock let me go ahead
and keep reading put no fire under and
then start praying so they took the
Bullock which was given them they
dressed it and called on the names of ba
from morning until evening until noon
saying oh Baal hear us but there was no
voice nor any that answered and they
leaped upon the altar which was made now
watch this Elijah starts to make fun of
them he's like your God is probably
sleeping and now I want you to know this
is what I want you to focus on and they
cried aloud and cut themselves after
their manner with knives and lancets
till the blood gust out on them watch
this and it came to pass when midday was
passed and they prophesied until the
time of the offering of the evening
sacrifice that there was neither Voice
come back with me for a moment please
what did these false prophets do what
were they doing all day they were
prophesying the prophesying was
something that that they looked at as a
miracle is about to happen so what the
Bible is telling us beloved one of the
things the Bible is telling us is that
through false prophecy look at the
screen through false prophecy and false
prophets this system will convince
people that this is of god let's go to
the screen let's go to the screen
prophets you ask are there false
prophets out today like doing this
pastor let me just show you I want you
to take a look at the amount of books
all of these books have been written by
socalled Prophet are y'all listening to
me all of these books the global reset
God I love you God and Donald Trump I'm
G say it I'm G just read the title of
the book Trump's prophetic Destiny Trump
2019 and Beyond the Oracle God's chaos
candidate God's chaos code Trump
apocalypse The Harbinger come back with
me for a moment y'all I need y'all to
understand this all of these books that
you see and this is just a handful of
them these are books that have been
written in the last five to seven years
about how God listen to me how God is
GNA bring in a wave of religious revival
that is going to take over the American
Nation and make it a Christian Nation
I'm not making this up literally what
the Bible said is happening right before
our eyes right now this is how America
is in Prophecy and these Pro these
so-called prophets are having visions
and you go on YouTube and just type in
Vision concerning America and you will
see all of the so many so-called
prophets talking about visions that
they've had of who's going to be the new
president and who's going to be the new
house Speaker yeah and who's going to be
all and and all of it is pointing to a
religious
takeover of the government of the United
States of America have you ever heard of
the seven Mountain mandates you may have
never heard of the seven Mountain
mandate let me put it up on the screen
the seven Mountain mandate known as 7M
is a prophecy or the seven Mountain
prophecy is a strategy for evangelizing
the modern world and enlarging Christ's
Kingdom it has especially gained the
following in charismatic and Pentecostal
churches those who follow the seven
Mountain mandate believe that the best
way for the church to be effective is to
bring change in the seven major spheres
of influence in society you may have
heard of these the education Mountain
the religious Mountain the family
Mountain the business Mountain the
government Mountain the Arts and Med
arts and entertainment mountain and the
media mountain and the idea that is
being pushed by this seven Mountain
mandate is very simple the seven sectors
of society are thought to mold the way
everyone thinks and behaves to tackle
societ societal change these Seven
Mountains must be transformed the
mountains are also referred to as
pillars Shapers molders and spheres
those who follow the seven Mountain
mandates speak of occupying the
mountains invading the culture and
transforming or taking back Society for
example in the book The Seven Mountain
prophecy Johnny Eno writes this a
so-called Prophet writes this there are
twisting events and making them say
something they're not talking about the
media there's stings in their tals the
liberal agenda
is actually a twisted look at issues
resulting in a Twisted interpretation of
what would be a solution because of this
the enemy strategy is to fill this
mountain with humanistic liberal people
who become his most unwilling unwitting
Pawns in releasing his Venom have you
all ever heard of the Great Awakening
this is a movement beloved of different
religious entities churches political
right leaning systems who are come back
with me come back to the screen with me
who are seeking to find a way to defeat
the beast from the abyss they don't know
that's the name of it but what they
don't understand is that the devil is
behind both systems the devil is playing
both systems he's making the left go so
far left that the right in anger and in
frustration will seek to set up exactly
what happened in the Dark Ages when the
Catholic Church ruled over Society all
right now we are ruling on behalf of God
this is a theocracy because we are
ruling on behalf of God and by the way
if you don't do what we say we have the
right to persecute you remember
Revelation 13 they will set up an image
and cause all to worship and whosoever
does not worship should be killed the
Bible beloved is not pointing to atheism
as the final enemy in the Bible it is
pointing to counterfeit Christianity as
the final adversary that is going to
force the whole world to worship and you
understand beloved that most Christians
today believe that God has tasked them
to make America great again look with me
on the screen Mike Flynn said these
words if we're going to have one nation
under God we must have we must is it up
on the screen if we're going to have one
nation under God which we must we have
to have one religion one nation under
God and one religion under God I'm not
making this stuff up y'all this is where
the Bible says America is headed setting
up a theocracy the Bible says in
Revelation 13:14 saying to them that
dwell on the earth that they should make
an image to the Beast which had the
wound by a sword and did live make an
image to the way that the papacy
operated during the Dark Ages which is
it was a church State entity with the
church ruling over the state the only
way to save our nation is to turn it
back to God we got to get rid of the
atheists we got to get rid of the
liberal we got to get rid of all these
people that are just turning against God
and the way we're going to do that is
through the use of political force which
introduces us to the latest project
which look on the screen with me is
called project
25 Pro 20 25 look on the screen and what
you're going to see is that this project
there's the website you can go check
this out for yourself this project the
goal of this project listen is to take
over the government and reshape it and
in fact here's what others are saying
about the project if Donald Trump wins
the 2024 election or even if some other
Republican end up in the White House
conservative groups are prepared to
destroy the federal government as we
know it and replace it with their vision
of a conservative
Christian Utopia that's not hypothetical
this is from the friendly atheist so
watch this y'all this is just crazy this
article is from a website called a
friendly atheist now here's the here you
have an atheist who believes that the
Bible is fantasy and yet the very thing
the Bible prophesied this atheist is
saying if this atheist only knew that
what he's warning against is actually in
the Bible man he might become Christian
isn't God good he just like what the
Bible prophesied this yes the Bible
prophesied it it's right there the book
you think is make believe the book you
think has no value the book you believe
is a fantasy foretold the very thing
you're warning about before you warned
about it so here it is people who do not
believe the Bible are literally saying
exactly what the Bible says without
realizing that they're saying exactly
what the Bible say come on y'all God is
trying to win him some atheist you
understand so check this out reading on
the right-wing Heritage Foundation
recently released a 920 page document
this is the project 2025 outlining their
plans for what they hope will be a
second Trump ter or a first ter for any
other Republican it's called project
2025 and it's a threat to anyone who
doesn't believe in Jesus or that
conservative extremist should control
every aspect of the government wow did
the Bible foretell this and is it
actually happening right before our eyes
listen to me in this 920 page document I
want you to notice one of the things
that they would like to do Under on page
589 under the title of Sabbath rest it
says God ordained the Sabbath as a day
of rest and until very recently the
judeo-christian tradition sought to
honor that mandate by moral and legal
regulation of work on that day and
they're talking about the first day of
the week remember if it was the Catholic
Church during the Dark Ages that changed
God's law and now the Bible is saying
that this system is going to make an
image a replica of the first Beast
during the Dark Ages look at what they
say look at what they say go back to the
screen moreover a share day off makes it
possible for families and communities to
enjoy time off together rather than as
atomized individuals and provides a
healthier cadi of life for everyone can
y'all believe this In America which is
supposed to be the land of religious
freedom they are seeking to implement a
Christian version by law which enforces
a false Sabbath and you want to tell me
that the Bible is not real you want to
tell me that the Bible is made up the
Bible is is is just a book of fantasies
all right we're almost there y'all we're
almost there I just need you to see this
just come to the screen the new speaker
of the house the let's go to the screen
and you just type this up research it
yourself Christian National the
Christian nationalism of speaker Mike
Johnson speaker Johnson has explicitly
embraced the idea that US the US was
founded upon particular Christian
principles in 2016 claiming we don't
live in a democracy it is a
constitutional republic and the founders
set that up because they followed the
biblical act on what a civil society is
supposed to look like let me read again
in the same interview he re he
reiterated his belief that the
separation of church and state is not a
constitutional principle over the last
60 or 70 years Our Generation has been
convinced that there is a separation of
church and state most people think that
is a part of the Constitution but it's
not what was the papacy it was a church
State entity what does protestantism
today want they want the elimination of
the separation of church and state the
church ought to be ruling the state and
when that happens beloved that's what
the Bible is warning is coming to
America verse 15 he had power to give
life unto the image of the Beast that
the image of the Beast should both speak
and cause that as many as would not
worship the enies of the Beast should be
killed in other words this Protestant
America will bring to life a church
State entity and all who do not go along
with it will be killed that's what the
Bible is saying 50 years ago y'all would
have been like farfetch it'll never
happen 20 years ago y'all would have
been like farfetched people don't want
to do that today I want to see how far
people are willing to go to defeat the
atheistic all right come with me we're
wrapping this up we're wrapping this up
Revelation 4:1 here's what I need you to
understand here's what I need you to
understand in Revelation 4:1 the Bible
says after this I looked and behold the
door was opened in heaven and the first
voice which I heard was as it were a
trumpet talking with me which said come
up hither and I will show unto thee
things which must be Hereafter so John
is taken up into heaven why is this
significant because the Bible tells us
in Hebrews 11:16 but now they that is
God's people desire a better country
that is a Heavenly wherefore God is not
ashamed to be called their God for he
has prepared for them a city I need you
to understand that the city that
Christians ought to be caring about all
to be concerned about is the Heavenly
Jerusalem put a one in the chat if y'all
get what I'm saying here it's the
Heavenly Jerusalem why because we are
citizens of that Heavenly Jerusalem
we're supposed to be Patriot
of that Heavenly Jerusalem we're
supposed to be Patriots of the Heavenly
Kingdom Come Again With Me to the screen
so John says immediately I was in the
spirit and behold a throne was set in
heaven and one sat on the throne and he
that sat was to look upon like a Jasper
and a sarden stone and there was a
rainbow round about the throne in the
sight like unto an emerald now he says I
beheld and lo in the midst of the throne
Revelation 5:6 and of the four beasts
and in the midst of the elders stood a
lamb as it had been slain now let me ask
you a question if I were to ask you what
is the symbol of this heavenly Nation
what animal is the symbol of this
heavenly Nation what would you say you
would say the lamb is the symbol of this
heavenly Nation so in essence then
beloved you and I are called yes to be
Christian
nationalists not Christian nationalists
but Christian nationalists this and note
this in John
18:56 or verse 36 Jesus answered and
said my kingdom is not of this world if
my kingdom were of this world then would
my servants fight that I should not be
delivered to the Jews but now is my
kingdom not from hence are y'all
following me true Christian nationalism
is about the Kingdom of Heaven not about
making America a Christian Nation
because America America can never be
heaven on Earth not America not France
not Rome not Jamaica not Spain nowhere
on Earth can ever be Heaven on Earth not
even Hawaii and I love you Hawaii but
you get the idea God's to be a true
Christian nationalist is to be all about
the kingdom of heaven but the devil
counterfeited that with this beast from
the earth that looks like a lamb now
watch this when John sees lamb he saw a
lamb as it had been slain like this lamb
was willing to die and die because he
loved us whereas the beast from the
earth this lamb it just looks like a
lamb but it speaks like a dragon there's
a huge difference there beloved between
these two Nations between the nation of
America and the nation of Heaven there's
a huge difference now listen don't get
me wrong I believe that America was
raised up for a very special purpose to
allow religion to go unfettered but the
Bible Pro prophecy is specifically
speaking about protestantism within
America that claims to serve God and
worship God and yet acts like a dragon
yet is willing to tolerate dragonis Ms
yeah I made that word up is willing to
look like a lamb but speak like a dragon
act like a dragon God is calling us to
be about the mission of the Heavenly
Nation that's what true Christian
nationalism is that's what true
religious patriotism is it's patriotism
to the kingdom of heaven and what is the
mission of the Kingdom of Heaven come on
we're almost done Revelation 14:6 the
Bible says here and I saw another angel
fly in the midst of Heaven having the
Everlasting gospel to preach unto them
that dwell on the earth and to every
nation and Kindred and tongue and people
every nation and Kindred and tongue and
people every nation Kindred tongue and
people why because no Nation Kindred
tongue or people are living up to what
you're about to hear following notice
with me verse six saying with a loud
voice fear Fe God and give glory to him
for the hour of his judgment is come and
worship him that made Heaven the Earth
the sea and The Fountains of waters
beloved listen America if because we
know this message is going to the whole
world including America you know what it
means no Nation on Earth is a Godly
Nation we need to get that out God has
called us to win the kingdoms of Hearts
he's not called us to win governments
and this is the mistake of Christian
nationalism this is the mistake of
protestantism cuz listen when you lack
the spirit you must then depend on Force
let me say that again when you cannot
convert because you lack the spirit the
only way for you to convert is through
the use of force and because
protestantism lacks this protestantism
lacks the spirit to convert because
you're teaching error you're teaching
things that are not in the word of God
you're doing things not in the word of
God and people are looking going yeah I
don't want that so now the only way left
to convert is by making it law when you
lack the spirit you're going to make
that up in force and that's what's
happening in this nation right now
that's what Christian churches and
Christian and and religious
conservatives in this country are
pushing for right now make it law in
Matthew 9:1 17 I got three more slides
and then we're done okay Matthew 9:17
Jesus said neither do men put wine into
new wine into Old bottles else the
bottles break and the wine rth out and
the bottles perish but they put new wine
into new bottles and both are preserved
Jesus here is talking about the
spreading of the Gospel right he's
saying you don't put old wine new wine
into Old bottles you got to put new wine
into new bottles he was talking about
the gospel going into the world as he
was pouring out this new wine into his
disciples the spirit and the reason that
it's important to understand that this
wine is symbolic of the teachings of the
Gospel is that Revelation 14:8 says
there followed another Angel saying
Babylon is Fallen that great great City
because she made all nations drink of
the wine of the wrath of her fornication
that wine is symbolic of false teachings
that wine is symbolic of false theories
and false understandings and Babylon who
is represented as a woman in the Book of
Revelation symbolizes that a a woman in
Bible prophecy is symbolic of a church
meaning this these are false churches
that are pushing false teachings and
false ideologies false concepts of what
it means our last text is Jesus's appeal
to us it says after these things in
Revelation 181 after these things I saw
another Angel come down from heaven
having great power and the Earth was
lightened with his glory and he cried
mly with a strong voice saying Babylon
the great is fallen and has become the
habitation of devils and the hold of
every foul spirit and a cage of every
unclean and hateful bird for all nations
have drunk of the wine of the wrath of
her fornication a and the kings of the
Earth have committed fornication with
her and the merchants of the Earth are
waxed Rich the abundance of her
Delicacies and now watch this and I
heard another voice from Heaven saying
come out of her my people that you be
not partakers of her sins and that you
receive not of her plagues all right
here's what I need you to understand
first of all you want the slides scan
right there you'll get the slides you'll
see them up on the screen you'll see
them up on the screen God God has
sincere people that are being misled by
these false systems and in this one of
these final messages in the Book of
Revelation is God's call to his people
that are in those systems he says come
out of her my people that tells me that
God has people who are sincere who are
devout but who are just misled they
don't understand was they look at the
enemy they look at atheism they at this
rise of of just anything goes and they
want to do what's right but the devil is
leading them in the wrong way to do
what's right and God has put all of this
has for warned all of this in the Book
of Daniel in the Book of Revelation so
that yes this doesn't mean come out of
America that's not what the prophecy is
saying remember it's not America itself
that is this Beast that is symbolic of
mystery Babylon it is the false
teachings within the religious the
Christian element within this nation and
so in their overreaction to try to get
rid of atheism and those things that
that that found their launching path out
of the French Revolution the left as it
were listen they are responding in a way
that is not in accordance with the word
of God and so God is telling us come out
of her my people not out of America out
of the false system of religion within
this country and that is going to spread
and that is spreading around the whole
world there are many things that I can
cover that talk that that will help you
to see see how this is going to happen I
don't have time to go into that today
but all I can tell you is this the Bible
is coming to pass with a rapidity that
is breathtaking the things that are
happening in our country today the Bible
foretold and for many years we' be like
it's coming it's coming it's coming and
beloved I can say this we are here right
now we are watching these things unfold
before our very eyes and it's time for
us to get ready to be ready because the
coming of the Lord is Drawing Near we
don't know when and we're not going to
say right we're not going to oh I think
it's but all I know is this these
prophecies are unfolding we're seeing it
before our eyes it's time for us to get
ready and I'm inviting you if you are
hearing this for the first time research
this don't just be like oh Pastor said
it and so it's true resch you may even
not not know who I am research
everything you just heard and my appeal
is this once you've done that and you're
like oh this is real this is true then
respond to the leading of the Holy
Spirit that's my appeal that's my call
heavenly father thank you for speaking
to us thank you for taking us through
this study of the word and Lord I pray
for those who are watching and who will
watch Lord that as they their eyes are
opened by the two witnesses who are
witnessing even now they were they
sought to put them to death during the
French Revolution but they're still
doing their work now Lord please may the
law and the testimony May the word of
God May the old and the New Testament
continue to do its work in testifying
and drawing people to you and exposing
the sin of Babylon exposing the corrupt
nature of this Beast with the horns of a
land that speaks as a dragon Lord please
enlighten your people who are in these
Fallen systems who are in these Fallen
churches Lord may they see the truth and
respond is my prayer in Jesus name amen
and amen